You are trying to erase black people, and a lot of black people wouldn't mind some of that erasure as long as that black person is Clarence Thomas.
A billionaire named Harlan Crowe is flying Clarence Thomas all over the world on unreported trips like an Instagram model, taking Clarence to the Maldives and the beaches and all.
Pay for his mama's house, this billionaire. Pay for Clarence Thomas' mama's house.
I got to give it up to billionaires. Billionaires, boy, y'all, y'all are relentless. Y'all always come up with something new to buy.
Like, just when you think of everything you could buy on Earth, a billionaire will come up with a new thing.
Y'all can buy space rockets, you can buy Twitter. This man bought a Supreme Court justice.
Do you understand how rich you have to be to buy a Supreme Court, a black one on top of that?
There's only two in stock, and Harlan Crowe owns half the inventory.
We can all see Clarence Thomas, but he belongs to billionaire Harlan Crowe.
And that's what an NFT is.
And that's all I can do, we can all see.
Obrigate to you.